acronis.com 2012-12-09

# Acronis Privacy Statement

  * Company Information
  * Board of Directors
  * Management
  * Contacts
  * International Contacts
  * Worldwide
  * Newsroom
  * Section 508 compliance
  * Careers
  * Submit Feedback

Have questions?

### Online Solution Wizard

Get answers

### Newsletter

* * *

| 

Acronis really respects your privacy, exactly as it is declared in company privacy statements. Acronis wants you to feel secure when visiting our website and providing information to us. Acronis will only gather your personal information with your consent.

This Privacy Statement has been prepared to inform you of the information we gather and how we use it. This Privacy Statement applies to all Acronis websites and agreements that display or link to this Privacy Statement. Some information may also be collected off-line, and this Notice applies to the off-line data collection as well.

#### What we collect:

Generally, you may visit our websites without providing any personal information or identifying yourself. We only collect customer information via the "opt-in" method, where visitors or customers must affirmatively elect to provide Acronis with their information.

In order to provide you with relevant information, respond to your requests, and increase the benefits that you receive from our website, we sometimes request that you provide us with information about yourself. Acronis requests customer information at various locations on our website, www.acronis.com, including product registration areas, promotional sign-up areas, and newsletter registration areas. The type of information collected may include standard contact information such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, and technical or demographic information.

Our website may also collect certain information from your visit and from your behavior while visiting our website, including the date and time of your access, the pages you have accessed and the name of the Internet Service Provider and/or Internet Protocol Address by which you are accessing the Internet, and the Internet address(es) from which you linked to our website, if applicable. This information is used to better understand how our website is being used in order to improve the quality of our website, and to enable us to comply with agreements between Acronis and referring or linked websites.

#### How we use your information:

We use this information to customize your website experience by delivering the content and information that we believe would be of interest to you. This information is also used to inform you of the latest Acronis developments, including new product releases, upgrades, special offers and other relevant information.

The information we collect is intended for Acronis business purposes only. In certain instances, we may make your information available to third parties that are providing services on our behalf. Acronis will only provide those third parties with information that is necessary for them to perform the services and who have agreed to take measures to protect your information that are at least as stringent as the measures that we take ourselves. We may also disclose your information to our business partners, for marketing and other business purposes, and as a result we or our business partners may communicate with you from time to time via email, telephone or physical mail. If at any time you tell us that you no longer wish to receive these communications, they will be halted promptly. Acronis is a global company with customers and partners in over 90 countries worldwide. Accordingly, any personal information we may collect may be used, stored and processed in the United States or in other countries where Acronis or our business partners have offices in or does business. By providing information to Acronis, you are consenting to the transfer of the information outside of your respective country to any other country throughout the world.

Acronis may disclose information that has been collected from you if we are required to do so by law or to protect the rights of Acronis, its employees or its business partners.

Certain Acronis products contain features that permit file sharing or synchronization with other users of Acronis products. If use these features, you acknowledge and agree that (i) you consent to the disclosure of the transferred information to the recipient, (ii) the transfer (and the transferred information) is in compliance with all of the terms and conditions of the Acronis Software and Services, (iii) Acronis is not responsible for the transferred content or for the complete, accurate or error-free transfer itself.

#### Removal procedures

As all information is collected via opt-in methods, we believe all information you receive from Acronis will be relevant to your computing needs. However, if you do not wish to receive communications from Acronis, simply visit https://www.acronis.com/my/subscriptions/ and check the **"Don't send me any messages"** option.

You can also change and/or update your profile including your contact information at https://www.acronis.com/my/profile/.

#### Cookies:

www.acronis.com utilizes cookies (small amounts of data stored by your Web browser on your hard drive) to help enable us to offer you more personal and customized content and service. These cookies also allow Acronis to track usage patterns and allow us to continuously improve and manage our website and deliver content that is specific to your interests. Most Web browsers accept cookies by default, but if you choose not to accept them, you can simply change your browser settings. If you decline to accept cookies, you may not receive the full benefits that our website has to offer.

#### Security

Acronis strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choice for its intended use. We have taken steps to secure and safeguard the information that we collect online, including the use of proven and effective security solutions, including SSL. However, the internet is an open forum and data may flow across multiple networks with inferior or no security measures, and therefore information may possibly be accessed by third parties other than those you intend to access it.

#### Business Relationships:

This website may contain links to other websites or logos from other companies. Acronis is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on any such websites.

#### Forums:

Portions of this website make forums and message boards available to its visitors. ANY AND ALL INFORMATION THAT IS DISCLOSED IN THESE AREAS BECOMES PUBLIC INFORMATION AND ACRONIS IS NOT OBLIGATED TO ENSURE THE PRIVCY OF THIS INFORMATION. PLEASE USE APPROPRIATE DISCRETION AND CAUTION WHEN DECIDING TO DISCLOSE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION.

#### Contacting Acronis:

If after reading this statement, you have any questions about Acronis' privacy statement; please submit your questions to Acronis Customer Service at http://www.acronis.com/support. Acronis may update or modify this privacy statement from time to time without prior notice to you, and each such update or modification becomes applicable immediately upon publication. Please review this notice often so that you can be aware of our latest policies on privacy and collection of personal information. Your continued use and visitation of the Acronis websites constitutes your consent to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, as amended from time to time.
